(Penny:)Okay, you've got my number.
Now give me the picture.
All right. You drive a hard bargain...
(Stuart:)- ...but here.
- All right. So, um, just give me a call.
(Sheldon:)So Leonard, how are you enjoying
Anything Can Happen Thursday?
(Sheldon:)Look at that. That's a dent.
(Sheldon:)Thank you,
Howard "Ham-Fisted" Wolowitz.
Did you shut the TV off
in the middle of the Deep Space Nine...
...Star Trek: The Original Series
"Trouble With Tribbles" crossover episode?
(Leonard:)Apparently so.
(Sheldon:)Are you ill?
(Penny:)No.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Then is it fair to say that you're
experiencing some emotional turmoil...
(Sheldon:)...over the events involving Penny
earlier this evening?
(Leonard:)When did you pick up on that?